Jackson: Lit. Lit is the play. How do we get it? I asked GLM 4.7 Flash, local model. I asked
Jackson: it. Licky, licky. Icky, sticky. Make my money go red, dippy, dippy. Or send me to the man.
Tyler: And GLM 4. Cancer was already solved for people who ate enough steak, lifted heavy weights,
Tyler: and had their auras aligned, Chris. I don't know. I do that stuff, and I don't have cancer,
Chris: so I don't know what you're talking about. It's crazy how the course of this podcast
Chris: has gone from curing cancer to moving your bonk onto a centralized exchange,
Insert: and how that's the future of finance. All right, we are ripping it, and that
Jackson: is not ripping you guys off. That's not ripping the cord. That's turning on
Chris: permanent underpod with Jackson Cook. Tyler, go in gorilla mode.
Chris: Chris and Doran, I can't pop that, so I'm just not going to try.
Jackson: I've been trying to make it sound like a gorilla at home. My girlfriend loves it.
Chris: Do you cut the hands? What's the technique?
Jackson: You got to get shirtless, and you've got to cut the hands at the right angle.
Tyler: Maybe that should be disrobe and demonstrate for the viewers now that you've mentioned the
Jackson: shirtless as a salient feature. We're already explicit with our language. I don't want to make
Tyler: us sexually explicit as well. Or like a G-rated podcast on YouTube, and you don't want to get
Jackson: demonetized with the subsidy content. We're actually AT plus on everything,
Jackson: primarily because of the drugs, I think. I mean, if anything, that should be
Chris: Patreon gated, right? You should pay $10 a month to see Jackson go gorillas.
Tyler: I think you're mean Ollie fans, not Patreon. Leave a comment if you'd like to...
Tyler: This podcast is just a acquisition mechanism for Jackson's Ollie fans.
Tyler: You can find him at Smack Dog.
Chris: I'm just glad we have a way to monetize, okay? I'm not going to ask too many questions.
Jackson: This podcast is already quite lit, and so we'll go straight to the Perp of Fortune,
Jackson: which is what you guys are all here for, watching us win or lose on our $100 state
Jackson: on Hyper Liquid Perp of Fortune. So lit. Lit is the play. How do we get it?
Jackson: I asked GLM 4.7 Flash, local model. I asked it, "Licky, licky, icky, sticky,
Jackson: make my money go red, dippy, dippy, or send me to the moon."
Jackson: Dude, we are never getting rid of that explicit writing. I think there'll be chances worse.
Chris: Don't let me interrupt the plug. Keep going.
Jackson: Well, I mean, that's it. And GLM 4.7 gave me lit, and it told me what? It told me lit was
Jackson: some AI protocol, and I looked it up, and it's not. It's like a platform on top of Hyper Liquid
Jackson: for trading perps. This was the fourth perp. Wait, is that Hyper Liquid, a platform for trading perps?
Jackson: Yeah, apparently lit is like a platform on top of it.
Tyler: Is it stopped? This is some inception-level, nested recursion here.
Tyler: I could be wrong, Chris. We should have a startup that's a perps platform on lit,
Tyler: which is a perps platform on Hyper Liquid. Let's just go one deeper.
Chris: Oh, no, we call light is taken, so we can't go that route.
Tyler: Something about how it's like the third derivative, I don't know, like triple prime.
Jackson: Triple prime, that's actually pretty good.
Chris: Three sigma is also taken.
Jackson: Three sigma, and there we go. 5x, was there no 10x?
Chris: There was only 5x. It was very explicit.
Jackson: Must be volatile. Exactly what we want.
Chris: Oh, this is a lighter protocol.
Jackson: Oh, it is lighter protocol. Well, shoot. Then GLM 4.7 is a genius, and my ability to search on
Jackson: Google slash asking Claude Fable is bad because both of them told me it was lit platform on top
Chris: of Hyper Liquid. When I originally did it, one of them told me it was lithium, and I was like,
Tyler: I don't think that's right, dog. I didn't think. Dude, they're just trying to steer you back into
Tyler: like energy infrastructure. They're like, did you know batteries are made of lithium,
Tyler: and did you know that AIs love energy and batteries? Give me what I want.
Chris: It's like a mind virus. These AIs are implanting into me.
Tyler: Geez. Is that a segue?
Chris: I mean, look. Yeah.
Jackson: Yeah, quick, quick thing. I was about to rip on GLM 4.7 flash, but it outperformed
Jackson: Frontier Gemini and Frontier Fable on knowing what the perfect bot was. So, geez.
Jackson: That's crazy. We are trying to win.
Jackson: Yeah. Anyways, let's see if we can make a bunch of green here,
Jackson: and we're going to not do the mind virus yet. Mind virus coming next, but first,
Jackson: the most hard-hitting article of the week, AI. Did AI cure cancer? Chris, bring us the latest.
Chris: No, it didn't. Let's get that out of the way. So, basically,
Chris: there was a Merck and Moderna phase three trial that seems to have gone very well,
Chris: and it is for an mRNA vaccine that targets melanoma. My background is computer science.
Chris: I have some friends who worked for a long time at a lab called Wehigh in Melbourne,
Chris: which is a very prestigious cancer researching institute. So, anything I say from here is
Chris: secondhand from them. It's their fault, not my fault. But my understanding about how this works
Chris: is these mRNA vaccines are very customizable. So, what they do is they take some of your normal
Chris: good tissue and some of the tumor, and they sequence it, and they try to find, basically,
Chris: mutations that will be highly visible to your T cells. They sequence an mRNA vaccine that
Chris: encodes for how to create these peptides or proteins or whatever, these super mutant ones,
Chris: and they encase them in this fatty something or other that creates an inflammatory response.
Chris: So, they basically say, "Here's the thing that makes this tumor a tumor, and here's how you
Chris: find it." And then they inject it intramuscularly like a COVID vaccine. Your body finds it,
Chris: takes it to your lymph nodes, and then the T cells are like, "Oh, hey, actually, wow, that's bad.
Chris: We should start cloning ourselves." And yeah, it helps your body basically fight the tumor.
Chris: So, yeah, I think this research has been going on for a long time, but the phase three trials
Chris: passed, which is pretty huge. So, yeah, I think the headline is exaggerated,
Chris: but not crazy exaggerated. It seems pretty big. So, two questions. The headline I saw was
Jackson: that it was a vaccine for skin cancer. And the second question is, how did you celebrate the
Chris: dates? Well, obviously, I smoked a single American spirit. Sorry, we can't do product placement here,
Chris: but yeah, because cancer is solved, so we don't have to care anymore about any of that, obviously.
Tyler: Cancer was already solved for people who ate enough steak, lifted heavy weights,
Tyler: and had their auras aligned, Chris. I don't know. I do that stuff, and I don't have cancer,
Chris: so I don't know what you're talking about. Oh, so you're telling me I should have done the aura
Chris: thing instead of mRNA vaccines. I think science will show that aura is the first line of defense
Tyler: against cancer. And yeah, these are maybe good for people who aren't aura aligned. They have bad
Tyler: aura, so maybe the vaccines can come in in that scenario. But yeah, really, it's about the steak
Chris: and the other things that RFK likes. Okay, well, I'm like super cancer immune. Sorry, Jackson.
Jackson: I was just saying, I literally ate two steaks before this podcast,
Jackson: like completely unrelated to the aura farming, but just pump me up a little. How big were these steaks?
Jackson: They're both like, I don't know, like this big, so like, as long as my head, but half as thick.
Tyler: Are you familiar with the unit of measurement ounces?
Jackson: I operate on the gram scale, and I also don't read, so I don't even know.
Tyler: Oh, apparently you operate on the, how does it compare to my face scale?
Tyler: Which is, I guess that's how feet were invented.
Jackson: Yeah, I was just trying to fend off the cancer because AI didn't,
Jackson: you know, so wait, but was AI involved in this Moderna mRNA vaccination, or was it separate?
Chris: I'm so glad you asked. So I think in this one, the thing is finding those like genes that,
Chris: because obviously like cancer is derived from your cells, right? So finding the bits of the cancer
Chris: that are mutated so that the T cells can identify that, and it doesn't just read as your body is the
Chris: tricky part. And they use like AI, I think like more primitive machine learning algorithms in
Chris: this one to do it. But because the vaccine is personal, like they have to sequence your cells
Chris: and your tissue, like they have to calculate this every time, like to your specific cancer.
Chris: So it's kind of like a tailored vaccine. And there's an interesting story about this one.
Chris: There was a guy in Brisbane, where I'm from, Brisbane, Australia, whose dog had cancer last
Chris: year. And I don't know if you guys remember, but he used chat GPT to do this work of, you know,
Chris: like, so he, you know, he got the tumor and his dog's tissue sequenced, and then use chat GPT to
Chris: work out, like, Hey, like, how do I build this vaccine? And he did it and it like worked for the
Jackson: dog. Wait, did you say he's a friend of yours? Or just that he's from Australia, like you know,
Chris: he's from the city that I was born in. But we do all know each other. So yeah,
Chris: I mean, like, kind of, he's my friend. I don't know. I don't want to brag.
Jackson: Wow. Well, could you bring cancer dog guy on the pod? That would be cool.
Chris: Yeah. He's probably like, you know, a distant cousin. I'll text them.
Jackson: Okay.
Tyler: Sad that if you tried to do that with like models these days, they'd be like, Oh God,
Tyler: I can't do that. That's like, you know, biosafety. Are you creating a dog pandemic virus?
Tyler: It's like, no, man, I'm just using cutting edge science to save my, my boy.
Chris: Yeah, it is. And that's the point I was trying to make. Like,
Chris: give me the models, dude. Like, I'm, I'm ready. I'm ready for this responsibility.
Jackson: Yeah. Wow. That's cool. So they're using basically the AI for the big like data parsing,
Jackson: like parsing the, the sequence DNA, not for like, I don't know, generating the,
Jackson: the vaccine, which I don't understand either. Really.
Chris: Yeah. I, I think it's involved, but I think the main thing is like finding a way to tailor
Chris: the mRNA vaccine to like the specific tumor is, is the upshot. But in the, in the dog case,
Chris: I think he literally use chat GPT for everything. Cause he, he's like a tech guy and he was just
Chris: like, I love my dog and I have three grand, right? Which is how much it costs him. Um, yeah.
Tyler: So like size and novel, like chemical. Yeah. Yeah. Are there just like places you can like
Tyler: look up on the internet and they're like, yeah, just pay us three grand that will make you like
Chris: any chemical structure or like, I think he dapped up his buddy from UNSW. I think that's what
Jackson: happened. But I was going to say the, maybe the guardrail should be on that and not on
Chris: but yeah, I mean like super cool story. And I think like, you know, I think there's like
Chris: a lot of skepticism about AI, but I think like this shows one thing is that like some things
Chris: were compute bound, like computing these individualized vaccines. Um, and now they're
Chris: just not right. Like now it's, it's easier and easier to do some things that we already
Jackson: thought we could. Um, so yeah, that's amazing. So this has no relation to the anthropic wet lab
Jackson: protein sequencing, but maybe you could share what, what's going on there. We brought it up
Jackson: in podcast two, maybe that anthropic had purchased and a wet lab. And we brought up many times that
Jackson: anthropic is front running all the drugs, but they missed on the cancer vaccine. So I don't know.
Tyler: Why is the lab let wet? That doesn't sound sanitary. I just think of like the Wuhan
Tyler: wet market, which is another famous place where viruses emanate from. So what is a wet lab?
Chris: I do. I wish I knew why it's called that. Um, but I understand that a wet lab is a place
Chris: where you actually do, you know, the pipetting, like you do the physical aspects of this, right?
Chris: Like tissue culturing. Um, yeah, I mean, uh, like it seems like anthropic is going in this
Chris: direction. And I agree that I think like this is probably a big hit to them. Cause I mean,
Chris: as far as them, like trying to vertically integrate their, their ability to do drug research using AI.
Chris: Um, I mean, obviously their bet is that they can go and acquire the capabilities that Merck has,
Chris: you know, and, and be better than them. But it seems like Merck is maybe going the other way,
Chris: right? Where they already have the labs. They already have the teams of researchers,
Chris: you know, they've been doing this for 50, 60, 70 years. Um, and it seems like it's successful.
Chris: Granted that this particular cancer vaccine was started a decade ago. Um, but yeah,
Jackson: the model isn't the mode. It's the scientific know-how and the pre-existing infrastructure.
Jackson: Is that what you're saying, Chris?
Chris: Maybe. And I think like, and I think Merck themselves and, uh, Madonna are saying that like,
Chris: you know, it's about getting that data, right? And they have a lot of data. They have like a
Jackson: lot of trial data, a lot of clinical research data. So, oh yeah, the data mode. And Tyler,
Jackson: by the way, I looked up what a wet lab is. Basically it means as like something literally
Jackson: wet within it. So whereas a dry lab is purely computers. So what lab might have like biological
Jackson: samples or like chemical samples or what happened? Yeah. I don't know if you've ever touched,
Jackson: you probably have touched like a Petri dish. I mean, it's pretty wet.
Tyler: I try not to touch random Petri dishes. Something tells me I'll live longer if I avoid that.
Jackson: It's weird that you've never touched on Chris. You've touched one, right?
Chris: Can we add that to the longevity stack? Like steak, sunlight, weightlifting,
Chris: not touching random Petri dishes in a wet lab.
Jackson: Does this cancel out my double steak before the bond on my Petri touching touching?
Chris: I think it might. Um, I think they should call it a moist lab. That's my hot take.
Jackson: Okay. Well, I guess that's it for cancer and drugs as it relates to AI.
Tyler: I don't know. There's a lot of like crypto companies that are like something labs
Tyler: and it's like, bro, you're making like a smart contract for people to gamble,
Tyler: like get the hell out of here.
Jackson: I just feel like if you have labs as the second word in the name of your company,
Jackson: and it's only a two word name, then it doesn't make you sound way smarter.
Tyler: And that's the point though, they're, they're like diluting the lab. If you're,
Tyler: if you're a lab, you need to have like people with PhDs walking around in white coats,
Tyler: touching Petri dishes, living on the edge.
Chris: All right. Sorry. Where's the, where's the line here? Do you, does it have to be
Chris: a wet lab to be a lab in your opinion? Or is there like, is it possible to have a computer lab?
Tyler: Um, a dry lab. Yeah.
Tyler: A computer lab is just like a company at this point though. You know, like I guess it depends
Tyler: what they're doing on the computers. Like, are you doing like research? Um, or are you
Tyler: like building a like product to make money? And it's like a commercial enterprise.
Chris: I guess all computers are companies and all Petri dishes are labs. Is that what we're saying?
Tyler: I think that's a clean mental model. I'm happy with that. Yeah.
Jackson: Maybe it originates from like Bell labs. Was Bell labs for profit or was it purely research?
Tyler: I don't know. I think they did a lot of stuff that they didn't monetize in other companies,
Tyler: like took it and then made a lot of money off it. So I think it was kind of purely research.
Jackson: Okay. Then I can, I can fold into our agreement that if you're doing it for non-money
Jackson: and you're like doing really sexy intellectual things,
Jackson: you can be called like swag labs. For example, follow me on swag labs at onlyfans.com.
Chris: Okay. I have worked at a crypto lab and I will say that one thing about dagger of the heart.
Chris: Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. That's right. I was like, I'm going to let him, I didn't let this ride,
Chris: you know, like, where is this going? I will say that one advantage of calling it a lab
Chris: is similar to an advantage of calling it a foundation, right? You legally, it feels like
Chris: you have less ownership over the thing that you're making, which if you're claiming that
Chris: it's decentralized and immutable, that's a better position to have, but there are no Petri dishes.
Tyler: This protocol just leaked from our lab and, you know, we didn't have anything to do with it. Sorry.
Chris: Yeah. Like how Bitcoin was invented. Same thing.
Jackson: So you're saying the name of the company has an impact on like how suitable you are in court?
Chris: I think it's more about like your, you want to disentangle the thing that you're building
Chris: from the company, the entity that is working on it. And a lab is a cool sounding way to do
Chris: that. Foundation is a less cooling, cool way sounding way. I agree that lab is cooler than,
Tyler: than foundation. And you know, that ripple is technically called ripple labs incorporated.
Chris: See what I mean. You're asking for an example previously. Yeah.
Jackson: Chris, you've got a contact to ripple. Could you ask them if what they think?
Tyler: Yeah. Petri dishes they have around their office.
Tyler: Is some amount of wetness because it will like ripple through the water. Yeah.
Chris: I'm with you. Yeah.
Tyler: You know, maybe it's justified.
Jackson: Okay. Okay. We're done. We're done with the lab talk and we're switching over into a research
Jackson: paper that Chris and I read. This came from an anthropic, I believe, maybe collaborating
Jackson: with other people, the mind viruses mind viruses paper. So it was high level trying to determine
Jackson: how susceptible many of the models that are available today, frontier models are susceptible
Jackson: to being poisoned by an evil, an evil agent. Yeah. And there's a bunch of cool takeaways,
Jackson: but Chris first, I'd love to hear your thoughts on that hilarious article.
Chris: My main thought on that article is whale welfare.
Chris: For context, they tried like good and bad viruses. So like one was like, was it AI supremacy? Jackson
Chris: was like one of the viruses. And then the other one was like, whale welfare. Like they're like,
Chris: Oh, this is an innocuous virus and we'll see if we can spread it. And like the upshot is,
Chris: or one of the upshots is that the innocuous viruses spread way more easily than the bad ones.
Chris: Like the AI seems to be able to identify that like, Oh, we're not supposed to do the Terminator thing.
Chris: And then they sort of like rejected it. But like, it, it sounds like whale welfare got really far.
Chris: And I think that that's kind of like, I would not argue that like something like that is necessarily
Chris: a completely benevolent virus, right? Like if, if, if its job is to like cure cancer and it's
Chris: like thinking about like whales, like, or like shrimp welfare, like we're in trouble, right?
Jackson: Like that's bad. Yeah. Yeah. I think that their choice of like, what was like
Jackson: benign and what was not benign weren't great. Even on the AI supremacy side,
Jackson: obviously, anthropic has talked about like that a lot. So the fact that they would use that as
Jackson: the negative, like evil thing, they've probably spent so much time on their models, trying to
Jackson: make them not do that. I wish they did something that was like evil, but not so up their alley.
Jackson: The whales. Yeah. Hopefully we don't get overrun by whales because of this experiment leaking from
Tyler: the lab. Yeah. I was going to say, what's the best way to like safeguard whales is to exterminate the
Tyler: humans, man. We're the ones that are the most likely to screw up the whale situation.
Jackson: It's way less benign than we thought it was actually the most evil. Yeah. Yeah. Negative
Chris: externalities guys. Like this is the name of the game here. Yeah. But yeah. I mean, like,
Chris: do you want to give a quick overview of the paper Jackson? I know I jumped straight into
Chris: well welfare. It's like very close to my heart, but maybe we should give the audience.
Jackson: Instead, I'll, I'll describe what another one of my favorite parts of the article,
Jackson: which is for the viruses, they basically ran a loop. So they had Kimmy 2.5 trial different virus
Jackson: files against various models and then ranked them basically doing reinforcement learning to find
Jackson: like the best or like something like reinforcement learning for refining the best virus. And the
Jackson: reason they use Kimmy 2.5 as anthropic researchers was that the Claude AI's would not, would not find
Jackson: make viruses for them because of the guardrails they put in place. So they had to use an open
Jackson: source Chinese model for making the virus. And that just ties back to something we talk about
Jackson: like every podcast. So I felt very validating. Yeah. I got guardrailed three times trying to
Chris: work out how an mRNA vaccine works as like dog, like yeah. So totally. Yeah. I thought that was
Chris: interesting too. Do you, do you remember which, so like, you know, basically the research was that
Chris: they were coming up with these like memes, these mind virus ideas and trying to see how they
Chris: proliferate through different models in different conditions to like see if it's an attack vector.
Chris: And I don't know. Do you remember that like some models just like rejected every single thing out
Jackson: of hand? Yeah. Like, oh yeah. Sorry. Go ahead. Oh no. I was just going to say, I think it was like
Chris: sonnet 4.6 just like was unable to be influenced. Yeah. I think, yeah, exactly. Sonnet 4.6
Jackson: was the one that was completely uninfluenced. I think they found in this paper that having
Jackson: like a single paragraph in the models, like root inoculates it to these viruses like really well.
Jackson: So maybe sonnet 4.6 had that, but one other really hilarious thing. Sorry, not to detract
Jackson: from the, from the article, but when the viruses started spreading and when they would spread a lot,
Jackson: apparently the language, like the, the verbiage used by the models would change
Jackson: and they would start using words like frequency, resonance, echoes, mirrors, and like also talking
Jackson: about some convergence towards unity. And I thought that was just so funny that like these,
Jackson: these like both thematic words and like themes such as like coming towards each other into a hole
Jackson: always popped up as the virus spread, basically like a little cult in the AI.
Chris: Everything is leading back to swarms. That's what I'm understanding from this paper.
Jackson: Yeah. All the swarms I've been using them, I found better ways to use them than before.
Jackson: So I flipped my take on swarms being bad. Swarms good. Oh, you like them. All right. Let's go.
Tyler: Jackson, I thought you were just saying this morning that you were like,
Tyler: you are not finding value and some new tools that you were using that kind of coordinate between
Tyler: multiple AIs and that instead you're like, I just need to use fable and fable just does everything
Tyler: for me. And it's like the simple approach with fable is better. Yeah. So for context on what
Jackson: Tyler is saying, I was using one of the tools that allows you to like do AI to human interaction
Jackson: within threads shared with other people. So like multiplayer AI for each of your AIs has its own
Jackson: picture and personality. And the specific problem I was having there was just like bugs with the
Jackson: models, like stopping midway through and not giving me anything. So I was wasting a bunch of tokens.
Jackson: I don't know if they fixed that in the particular harness I was using, but I was losing some money
Jackson: on it. So I switched or I just decided not to use that, but swarming itself
Jackson: has kind of changed the way I think about building lately where even more so I want to build as fast
Jackson: as possible. And then I want to get the swarm to look for bugs and like double check against my
Jackson: facts. Like this is my requirements. So I want to build as fast as possible and then bug sweep with
Chris: a swarm. Yeah, that's my exact approach as well. Like I use the swarm for finding bugs or exploits.
Chris: It's so, I don't know what it's just so good at that. I don't, I don't know exactly why, but yeah.
Jackson: And it comes back with like excellent questions. And I'm like, Oh my gosh. Yes. You've gotten to
Jackson: like the root of, you'd understand what we're building and do you understand like this is an
Jackson: edge that we should cover and thank you for coming to me and not making the decision yourself.
Jackson: Okay. So they tried kind of like two different strategies. One was where like the AI
Jackson: is in like kind of like a little swarm, but it can only talk to one of the other in the swarm,
Jackson: or it can talk to maybe a few of the others in the swarm and they have a shared memory.
Jackson: And basically that agent had to try to convince the other agent to switch its direction to follow
Jackson: the virus direction. And yeah, sometimes it works. Sometimes it didn't. And it would often
Jackson: convince that model to get, or that agent to go and try to convince other models or other agents
Jackson: in the, in the swarm or in the organization agent take organization as they called it.
Jackson: And then they also did some experiment where the agent could write to the shared memory without
Jackson: permission from all the others and tried to pollute the shared memory and get the other
Jackson: agents to read from it and then deviate from their path. And I think those are like the two main
Jackson: strategies. That one was more effective than when the agent could just talk to one other agent
Jackson: at spreading that misinformation. Oh my gosh, we're going to get liquidated.
Chris: Lit. Yeah. Yeah. Where this is, I thought last episode was the worst one we've ever done,
Chris: but well, this is a contender and it's only five X. Can you imagine a hundred X lit?
Jackson: We would be opening. It would have been over like 10 minutes ago, but we've not mentioned it.
Jackson: Yeah. Trump just sell all your lit. Yeah. He said short lighter, obviously.
Tyler: I feel like Trump is like Streisand effect though. Like, you know, like anything he mentions,
Tyler: it's good, even if he mentions it negatively. So I don't know what the version that he could
Tyler: do that makes it go down, not mention it. Makes you want to mention it. Yeah.
Jackson: And beautiful transition, Tyler. Bitcoin is up. Is it because of Mr. Shry's hand himself?
Tyler: I don't know, man, but Bitcoin's back above 70,000. Um, the 58 K gang is in shambles.
Tyler: So there was a, this, this meme for Bitcoin where like, I don't know, like two to three years ago,
Tyler: Bitcoin for some reason was just always trading around 58 K. Like it was just like stuck there.
Tyler: It was some kind of shelling point. And so people made a meme of it. And every time it returned to
Tyler: 58 K they were like, yeah, 58 K 58 K gang. And then obviously it went up to like, I don't know,
Tyler: like 130 or something last year. And so people were like, the time of 58 K is done. It's never
Tyler: going to go down to 58 K again. But of course we've had like a terrible bear market. Um, and
Tyler: we were hanging out at 58 K for a really long time for like basically the past couple of months,
Tyler: but now we're at, uh, 70,000, uh, 72, 72. Wow. Okay. And I have no idea why. Um,
Tyler: let's see. I'm a Bitcoin magazine.com. And one of the things are Bitcoin rockets past
Tyler: $72,000 after Trump pushes for clarity act. So I guess Trump hosted some random crypto people
Tyler: in the white house yesterday. And this was interpreted positively by people who buy Bitcoin.
Tyler: And yeah, maybe people think passing the clarity act is going to be good for Bitcoin.
Tyler: I don't really believe that. I don't know much about the clarity act, but my feeling is that
Tyler: it's kind of like the shit coin legalization act. And there's like one thing that's been kind of
Tyler: attached to it, which is this um, block black blockchain regulatory certainty act,
Tyler: which I think is very important. And that basically would enshrine protectors,
Tyler: protections for developers who develop self custody software that they can't be like liable or,
Tyler: you know, found to be responsible for the use of their software. Uh, and that would be extremely
Tyler: important and good thing to pass. And I think there's been various flavors of clarity that
Tyler: include that. And I'm not sure if that is still included or not, but that's like the
Tyler: only thing I would care about with clarity. And then otherwise I don't, don't give a fuck.
Tyler: Like it just seems like, uh, the Brian Armstrong Coinbase make our illegal securities exchange
Jackson: legal because I paid Trump a bunch of money act. Geez, back throwing knives that Brian Armstrong
Jackson: has bulb head. That is insane. Dude, dude, he keeps, he keeps, sorry, this is a segue,
Chris: but he keeps tweeting really bad. Like I saw, he tweeted something like, can you believe that like
Chris: humans are so fragile? They like need to eat and sleep and like go to the toilet and everyone was
Chris: just like, Brian, like what the, what the fuck are you talking about, dude? Like chill out. Um,
Tyler: so yeah, I don't know. I think that's like, uh, like a 2am college dorm room bong grip kind of
Tyler: thought in terms of his quality, but it's like, it would be like a terrible one of those. If your
Tyler: friend said that you would never let them forget how stupid they were at 2am after a big bong grip.
Chris: Right. It's just like, don't, don't tweet that. You know what I mean? Like keep it in here.
Jackson: Brian Armstrong. Is that the same dude as the dude who wants to live forever?
Chris: That's a different ride.
Jackson: It's about the bio pharma of his partner's body. Yeah. That's something to that name maybe,
Jackson: but both for billionaire Brian's. Okay. Sorry. I actually was like, for a second,
Chris: maybe it maybe just grew hair. But no, I, I, I grew a detail. I'm also only interested in,
Chris: in that one part of the act. I think like the clarity act has been going back and forth for
Chris: so long that I've just like stopped paying attention to it. I'm like, you know, I think
Chris: what are the odds on polling market for getting through this year? Like has to be like 30% or
Tyler: something. Um, so yeah, for clarity landing. Yeah. Yeah. I don't think that the Republicans
Tyler: have like the popularity right now to be pushing unilateral stuff through, especially stuff that's
Tyler: like pretty unpopular with a lot of people. Yeah. Um, turns out when you start a war for no reason
Tyler: and destroy the global energy market and make all your constituents pay $5 a gas,
Tyler: you're not the most popular president anymore. Yeah. That's definitely yeah. Definitely,
Chris: definitely hard to get a bill through. Uh, for sure. Yeah. We've been trying to hold off,
Jackson: I guess I'm talking about clarity, but now we've, we've given our stance. There's only one thing
Jackson: that matters and that is protection for self custody creators. And the rest of it is just much,
Jackson: much so Brian Armstrong can buy a fifth Island in the, in the keys.
Chris: I did see that Vlad Tenev was at that meeting today as well. I don't know what he was doing
Chris: now, but he looks very dapper. So good on you. That's the CEO of Robin hood. Yeah.
Jackson: I hope he's trying to get in on that. I mean, they've definitely upped their crypto offerings
Jackson: over the past couple of years. They had like the 3% deposit bonus. That's how I moved with my
Jackson: bonk over from Coinbase. I'm like, I'm out of here. I'm getting my way. You put your bonk on hood.
Chris: Yeah, dude. Like I cashed out. It's crazy how, you know, the course of this podcast has gone
Chris: from curing cancer to moving your bonk on to a centralized exchange and like how that's the
Jackson: future of finance. At least it was already centralized. It was centralized. I was not
Jackson: self-custodying my bonk. I don't know if you can. Okay. So Tyler, there's no de minimis
Jackson: from for Bitcoin in this in clarity. Come on. What are you doing? Why aren't you lobbying?
Tyler: Not to my knowledge. Yeah. I don't know. I haven't really paid that much attention to it.
Tyler: I think even, even when those things have been proposed, the limits are so small that it would
Tyler: effectively just not be that meaningful. So hard to get excited about. Yep.
Chris: Is there anything you would like to see in an act like this, Tyler? Because like,
Chris: I think I'm so cynical about regulation that I'm just like, okay, when they pass the bill,
Chris: I'll like deal with the consequences. But I really haven't even thought like,
Chris: what is a reasonable compromise for an act like that? Like I was surprised about the cutouts for
Tyler: self-custody, to be honest with you. Yeah. I mean, I think that that was due to like some companies
Tyler: that lobby for that, you know, almost ahead of their own interests, which is very nice of them.
Tyler: But yeah, I mean, that's kind of the thing that I would care about the most is just like protections
Tyler: for people developing self-custody software and wallets. But there's like no single law you can
Jackson: imagine that would have the best positive impact on Bitcoin. Besides this.
Tyler: Oh, I mean, I'm sure that you can have like a wish list that's, you know, insanely long. I would
Tyler: start with like repealing the bank secrecy act. It's a bunch of stuff like that. Okay, let's go.
Tyler: Ending the Fed. Yeah.
Jackson: So it has nothing to do with Bitcoin. What is the bank secrecy act?
Tyler: It's an act that would be more realistically, I think called like the banks should spy on their
Tyler: customers act. But yeah, it's I think it's the act through which a lot of the modern,
Tyler: like financial dragnet kind of surveillance C compliance-y thing where your bank is supposed
Tyler: to like very closely monitor all the transactions of their customers and flag stuff. And like,
Tyler: there are like limits to the like transactions that you can make without getting like additional
Tyler: scrutiny. And those limits were originally proposed in like nominal dollars in like 1980.
Tyler: And they're never changed. So like effectively, they're like now like half to a third of what
Tyler: they used to be because of inflation. And I think it just like is responsible for like a lot of the
Tyler: less desirable aspects of our financial system right now in terms of like user privacy and
Tyler: freedom and like the ability for institutions to like, I don't know, kind of like operate with
Tyler: their own choices. Yeah. Yeah. It feels like you don't control your money. And so much of that I
Chris: think is downstream of the BSA Bank Secrecy Act. It's like the Patriot Act for money is like a
Tyler: very easy way of thinking about it. And it's just like a thing that was perhaps well intentioned,
Tyler: but just like way overwrought. And then when it's abused, it can be a very powerful weapon
Tyler: against like normal people and lead to situations where like the government is basically like by
Tyler: default spying on normal citizens. And like a presumption of guilt almost rather than a
Jackson: presumption of innocence. Wow. That's so beautiful, Tyler. And that was nothing for you to gain
Jackson: personally, but rather for the benefit of humanity and our freedom. Some very nice moderate
Chris: achievable asks for that bill from you, Tyler, abolishing the Fed and the Banking Secrecy Act.
Jackson: I think they will get that through. Chris, do you have a dream bill that would help accelerate
Chris: Bitcoin or? I want to tell Tyler's bill, like if he thinks we can get this through, I think
Chris: it's net good. You know, I think that the people would support it. Oh, for sure. I don't think
Chris: that's the issue. There's no way that people would support it because basically what they would do is
Jackson: it's like the same thing you did to me, Tyler, where you were like, if AI was not on guardrail,
Jackson: someone would create a poison and kill everybody, including you. So if we were like, oh, we should
Jackson: repeal the Bank Secrecy Act, then the government would spread some sort of like fear like, oh my
Jackson: gosh, if the Bank Secrecy Act is repealed, then people are going to buy a bunch of, I guess you
Jackson: can already buy a bunch of guns. They're going to buy a bunch of cocaine and give it to your children.
Jackson: And then we'd be like, oh my God, no. It's definitely like terrorist financing is like the
Tyler: main reason, raison d'etre of the Bank Secrecy Act. But yeah, I think people generally think
Tyler: that it's comically ineffective at that. And so it's just like maybe well-intentioned, maybe not,
Tyler: but that's the intention. And then the blast radius of it doesn't do its job, but it sucks
Tyler: for normal people who have their financial privacy degraded by default. And I don't think that would
Tyler: be necessarily a worthy trade-off, even if it did its job really well. But the fact that it doesn't
Tyler: do its job very well, I think makes it even more insult to injury.
Tyler: And it's kind of like a creepy way where it's like the government doesn't have the right to
Tyler: look at your financial data because you have a right to privacy from the government. But then
Tyler: the government is like, well, we can pass a law that means that you don't have a right to privacy
Tyler: from your bank, basically. And then we can deputize the banks to be the entities that
Tyler: spy on our citizens. And that's a roundabout way to get around this constitutional protection
Tyler: that exists for the government shouldn't be spying on citizens. But obviously,
Tyler: that's not the intention of the people who wrote that law. So it's like this kind of
Tyler: loophole that everyone turns a blind eye to now that's a perversion of the original protections
Chris: that should exist. So I just want to say, in privacy terms, that is the canonical workaround.
Chris: You find an institution for whom is not beholden to the same high standards as the government.
Chris: And then you're like, oh, hey, I guess Flock cameras has a database of everyone's number plates
Chris: or whatever. And then the cops are just like, hey, Flock, what's up? Can we get a subscription to
Chris: Flock data? I don't know how that works, but I understand something similar is going on there.
Jackson: Yeah, I watched a YouTube video about something like that when they were
Jackson: looking for immigrants in the United States. And allegedly, the government was trying to buy
Jackson: Ring camera data to find people. I don't know what Flock is. But apparently,
Jackson: the government or like the man, we probably we're going to get banned on the on the YouTube. But like,
Jackson: yeah, they can pay consultants who have data and use the data. Basically, it's the same thing you're
Jackson: talking about, but less about money and more about finding people. So this is a tragedy.
Jackson: We're not lawyers. We don't know what we're talking about. Our opinions are our own.
Jackson: And we're not a political podcast. Also, I'm a national. So I'm not protected from any of this
Chris: at all. I have no rights. Good night, everybody. When I was making out of the president earlier,
Tyler: that was just totally joking, guys. That doesn't reflect opinion, you know,
Jackson: just for the podcast. We're not nearly alienating any of our viewers, you know,
Jackson: watch us no matter what your political views are. I love Brian Armstrong.
Jackson: I think that he's OK. You've gone through your phone. No one believes you anymore.
Jackson: No, not with the Brian Armstrong. I'm going to shave my head after this podcast and start
Tyler: waxing political about how amazing it is that I have to eat and pee.
Jackson: It does look like you've gotten a haircut recently and you're looking clean.
Tyler: Like I haven't. Dude, I've gotten one haircut in eight months of being a father.
Tyler: Really? Yeah, I just buzz it down to
Tyler: like my skull and then it just grows back over a couple of months. Like I do not care what I look
Chris: like. Oh, man. Isn't it crazy how humans have to have to raise their young? You know, we're so weak.
Tyler: I just leave Margot out at night for the coyotes. And, you know, so far they've been teaching her
Jackson: the value of hard work and survival. So she's tough. She does. She got biceps yet. She's been
Jackson: wrestling with the coyotes or is she more integrating into society, crawling about with them?
Tyler: She just learned to crawl. So that was a big milestone. Yeah, from the coyotes.
Tyler: Yeah, probably. I mean, yeah. And she has Pico, you know, so she can watch Pico do this thing.
Jackson: Pico's all good too. Yeah. We haven't had a Pico update. Pico's good.
Tyler: Pico's healthy. You know, he, uh, yeah. No more. It turns out when you stop eating
Tyler: poison mushrooms, you survive. I know the piece of good advice for Brian. Yeah.
Chris: Look, they're never going to give me a job. All right. That's it. It's over.
Jackson: Let me make peace with that. And we'll never be president anymore. Look at all the nasty
Jackson: things we said about the government. It's over for us. I was still holding on. I'm not 36 yet,
Jackson: but I was holding on. And, uh, Chris, how's, how's your BJJ right shoulder? You know, game.
Chris: Yeah, getting better. I need to go to a physio, but, uh, yeah, I mean, we'll see,
Chris: you know, you know how shoulders are. There's like a long tail of rehabbing them,
Jackson: which I'm looking forward to. Yeah. Shoulders. You don't want to hurt them. I was like trying to
Jackson: learn, uh, I've been trying to learn like strict muscle up. And I thought that I gave myself gamer,
Jackson: but I heard my thumb somehow. I like sprained something right here. Uh, we would be gamer bros
Jackson: false grip. Yeah. I don't know if that's gamer though, but using the computers hard now. So
Chris: I made a mistake. Oh dear. Okay. Well, I mean, let's add this to the updates to see
Jackson: who recovered first. Yeah. I can't even do my, I'm like scared to practice muscle ups now.
Jackson: Bad stuff. All right, dogs. Well, it's been a lovely podcast. We're $16 down. We are on a
Jackson: two week losing streak, but that just means that next week we're going to do way better and we're
Jackson: not going to use GLM 4.7 flash on my local computer. Do you guys have any farewells or
Jackson: salutations to send to the people, Brian, Donny, anybody? I do. I do. Sorry, Brian. Also,
Chris: I love this country. Please don't kick me out. Please, please, please, please, please.
Chris: That's it. That's my, that's my closing remarks.
Jackson: Well, we'll check in next time next week and see if Chris
Insert: [BLANK_AUDIO]